{
    "subject": "resource/Toronto",
    "predicate": "ontology/leaderName",
    "object": "resource/John_Tory",
    "human_readable": "The leader of Toronto is John Tory.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9726169109344482,
            "question": "Is John Tory currently leading Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9225614666938782,
            "question": "Is John Tory responsible for governing Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.86541348695755,
            "question": "What is John Tory's position in Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8503909707069397,
            "question": "In what city is John Tory the leader?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.818923830986023,
            "question": "Who is the leader of Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8094505667686462,
            "question": "What role does John Tory hold in Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7039202451705933,
            "question": "Name the current leader of Toronto."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6867019534111023,
            "question": "What is the name of the leader of Toronto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6691086292266846,
            "question": "What city does John Tory lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6404398679733276,
            "question": "Who holds the position of leadership in Toronto?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The leader of Toronto is John Tory.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7542_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city does John Tory lead?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7542_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the leader of Toronto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7542_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the current leader of Toronto.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7542_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7542_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple mentions of John Tory as the Mayor of Toronto throughout the files (files 82, 29, and others).\n* One file (file 73) explicitly states \"John Tory, the 65th Mayor of Toronto...\".\n* Another file (file 84) confirms that John Tory is indeed the 65th Mayor of Toronto.\n\nTherefore, based on this information:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently refer to John Tory as the Mayor of Toronto, thus supporting the statement that he is indeed the leader of Toronto."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}